Guide to the U.S. Department of Labor Survey of Industrial Relations in the Steel Industry 1959
U.S. Department of Labor Survey of Industrial Relations in the Steel Industry
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
U.S. Department of Labor Survey of Industrial Relations in the Steel Industry, 1959
5186
U.S. Department of Labor
1 linear ft.
Records.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Survey of Industrial Relations in the Steel Industry, 1959. Collected by George P. Schultz.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Schultz, George Pratt, 1920-; United States. Department of Labor.
Form and Genre Terms:
Records
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
CONTAINER LIST
- Steel Study, The United Steelworkers and Union-Wide Bargaining, George Seltzer (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Steel Study, Report and Study Proposals, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Labor Education Materials (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Labor Education Materials (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Notebook for First Year Members, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Labor Education Materials, Steelworkers Institute Notebook, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Labor Education Materials, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Steelworkers Institute Notebook, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Notebook for the Steelworkers Institute, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Steel Study, Steelworkers Earnings, Postwar Period, M. Horowitz (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Steel Studies, Interviews, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Steel Study, Strike Experience in Selected Countries, A. Siegel (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Steel Study, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Profiles of Negotiation in Basic Steel, Appendix (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Steel Study, Steel Industry, Markets, Technology, Break-Even Points and Financing, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Collective Bargaining in the Basic Steel Industry, A Study of the Public Interest and the Role of Government (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Steel Study, Exhibits and Literature of Interest, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Steel Study, Productivity and Price Project, Louis Lister, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Steel Study, Historical Materials, Negotiations, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Steel Study, Fisher's, Steel Output and Wage Losses in Strikes of 1952, 1956, 1959, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Steel Study, Role of Collective Bargaining in Steel, Pattern Setter of Follower, Harold Levinson (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Steel Study, The Influence of Steel Price Increases on Inflation, Frank Norton, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- The Inland Steel Company Case, William F. Whyte, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Job Evaluation Information, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)